

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Amman, Jordan
- rimariyad98@gmail.com
- in @rimariyad
- +962788435324

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- •••• Problem Solving
- Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel)
- •••• Java
- •••• html
- •••• PHP
- •••• CSS, Bootstrap

LANGUAGES

- Arabic (Mother tongue)
- English (Conversational)

RIMA ALENIZY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a fresh software engineering graduate, with a focus on web development. During my studies, I acquired good programming skills, especially in object-oriented, front-end, and back-end. I had the opportunity to apply my knowledge in programming and problem-solving skills during several projects. Throughout my working experience, I had the chance to improve and apply my skills in the web development field through different projects. I obtained and enhanced many skills such as time and project management, teamwork.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Web development trainee

Orange digital village | Oct 2021 - present

- full-stack development
- Soft Skills Workshops

Save Lives (website)

Bachelor Project | Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

- Develop a blood donation Website.
- Front-End (HTML, CSS).
- Back-End (PHP).

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Software engineering

Zarqa University | Mar 2017 - Jun 2021

• GPA:84 / Excellent

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Team Work
- Problem Solving
- Self learning
- Hardworking